const GAME=[{question:"The capital of Belgium",answers:[{id:"1",value:"Brussels",correct:!0},{id:"2",value:"Zagreb",correct:!1},{id:"3",value:"Sofia",correct:!1},{id:"4",value:"Tallinn",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of Croatia",answers:[{id:"5",value:"Helsinki",correct:!1},{id:"6",value:"Zagreb",correct:!0},{id:"7",value:"Reykjavik",correct:!1},{id:"8",value:"Bratislava",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of North Macedonia",answers:[{id:"9",value:"Tallinn",correct:!1},{id:"10",value:"Skopje",correct:!0},{id:"11",value:"San Marino",correct:!1},{id:"12",value:"Belgrade",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of Liechtenstein",answers:[{id:"13",value:"Vaduz",correct:!0},{id:"14",value:"Nicosia",correct:!1},{id:"15",value:"Reykjavik",correct:!1},{id:"16",value:"Kyiv ",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of France",answers:[{id:"17",value:"Amsterdam",correct:!1},{id:"18",value:"Riga",correct:!1},{id:"19",value:"Paris",correct:!0},{id:"20",value:"Sofia",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of Denmark",answers:[{id:"21",value:"Belgrade",correct:!1},{id:"22",value:"Copenhagen",correct:!0},{id:"23",value:"London",correct:!1},{id:"24",value:"Minsk",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of Romania",answers:[{id:"25",value:"Belgrade",correct:!1},{id:"26",value:"Bratislava",correct:!1},{id:"27",value:"Sarajevo",correct:!1},{id:"28",value:"Bucharest",correct:!0}]},{question:"The capital of Ukraine",answers:[{id:"29",value:"Berlin",correct:!1},{id:"30",value:"SkoTbilisipje",correct:!1},{id:"31",value:"Kyiv ",correct:!0},{id:"32",value:"Pristina",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of Poland",answers:[{id:"33",value:"Warsaw",correct:!0},{id:"34",value:"Madrid",correct:!1},{id:"35",value:"Paris",correct:!1},{id:"36",value:"Dublin",correct:!1}]},{question:"The capital of Germany",answers:[{id:"37",value:"Lisbon",correct:!1},{id:"38",value:"Berlin",correct:!0},{id:"39",value:"Stockholm",correct:!1},{id:"40",value:"Pristina",correct:!1}]}],game2=document.querySelector(".game-2"),questions=document.querySelector(".game-2__questions"),result=document.querySelector(".game-2__results"),text=document.querySelector(".game-2__text"),question=document.querySelector(".game-2__question"),answers=document.querySelector(".answers"),indicator=document.querySelector(".game-2__indicator"),nextBtn=document.querySelector(".next"),restartBtn=document.querySelector(".restart");let results={},trueAnswer=0;const randomQuestions=t=>{randomIndicator(t+1),questions.dataset.step=t;questions.innerHTML=`
    <div class="game-2__question-item">
        <div class="game-2__question">${GAME[t].question}</div>
        <ul class="answers">${GAME[t].answers.map(e=>`
            <li class="answer-item">
            <label>
              <input class = "answer-input" type="radio" name= ${t} value = ${e.value} step = ${e.correct}>
              ${e.value}
            </label>
          </li>
            `)}</ul>
      </div>`},randomIndicator=e=>{indicator.innerHTML=e+"/"+GAME.length};game2.addEventListener("change",e=>{e.target.classList.contains("answer-input")&&(results[e.target.name]=e.target.value,results[e.target.step]=e.target.step,nextBtn.disabled=!1),"true"===e.target.step&&trueAnswer++}),game2.addEventListener("click",e=>{var t;e.target.classList.contains("next")&&(nextBtn.disabled=!0,(t=Number(questions.dataset.step)+1)===GAME.length?(nextBtn.style.display="none",restartBtn.style.display="block",questions.style.display="none",indicator.style.display="none",result.style.display="block",text.style.display="block",result.innerHTML=trueAnswer+"/"+GAME.length,10==trueAnswer?(text.innerHTML="you are genius",text.style.color="green",game2.style.background="green"):trueAnswer<=4?(text.innerHTML="go back to school",text.style.color="red",game2.style.background="red"):(text.innerHTML="not bad",text.style.color="rgb(255, 140, 1)",game2.style.background="rgb(255, 140, 1)")):randomQuestions(t)),e.target.classList.contains("restart")&&(randomQuestions(0),nextBtn.style.display="block",restartBtn.style.display="none",questions.style.display="block",indicator.style.display="block",result.style.display="none",text.style.display="none",game2.style.background="linear-gradient(315deg,rgb(95, 95, 233), rgb(239, 96, 96), rgb(228, 228, 112))")}),randomQuestions(0);